Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
- Box: 56, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - Item 2: Possibilities for International Co-Operation in the Study of Internal Migration, 1957; Publication (Box 56, Folder 43)
    Notes: February 12, 1957
- Box: 56, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Movement of Labor Between Farm and Nonfarm Sectors and Multiple-Jobholding by Farm Operators in the Tennessee Valley, 1967; Publication (Box 56, Folder 44)
    Author: National Fertilizer Development Center
- Box: 56, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 56, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Migration Flows and their Determinants, and the Effects of Return Migration, 1969; Publication (Box 56, Folder 45)
    Author: John Vanderkamp
  - Item 2: The Labour Market and the Intrafactor Allocation Mechanism in Canada, 1967; Publication (Box 56, Folder 45)
    Author: Mahmood A. Zaidi
- Box: 56, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 56, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Rural to Urban Migration: A Colombian Case, 1966; Publication (Box 56, Folder 46)
    Author: William L. Flinn
- Box: 56, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 56, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Mouvements de Population et Service Social, 1965; Publication (Box 56, Folder 47)
    Author: Congres de Bordeaux
- Box: 56, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 56, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Montana Labor Mobility Project, 1968; Publication (Box 56, Folder 48)
    Author: Montana Employment Service
    Notes: July 1, 1967 - December 31, 1968
- Box: 56, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 56, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Movement of Labor Between Farm and Nonfarm Sectors and Multiple-Jobholding by Farm Operators in the Tennessee Valley, 1967; Publication (Box 56, Folder 49)
- Box: 56, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 56, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: The Propensity to Move, Publication (Box 56, Folder 50)
  - Item 2: The Geographic Mobility of Labor, Publication (Box 56, Folder 50)
  - Item 3: Migration Into & Out of Depressed Areas, Publication (Box 56, Folder 50)
  - Item 4: Movement of Labor Between Farm and Nonfarm Jobs, 1966; Publication (Box 56, Folder 50)
    Author: Michigan State University
  - Item 5: Interstate Migration of Destitute Citizens, 1940; Publication (Box 56, Folder 50)
  - Item 6: The Western Areas Removal Scheme, 1953; Publication (Box 56, Folder 50)
    Author: South African Institute of Race Relations
  - Item 7: Migration and Changes in the Quality of the Labor Force, 1967; Publication (Box 56, Folder 50)
    Author: Thomas W. Gavett
  - Item 8: Geographic Mobility and Employment Status, 1963; Publication (Box 56, Folder 50)
  - Item 9: Interstate Migration and Wage Theory, 1961; Publication (Box 56, Folder 50)
    Author: Robert L. Raimon
- Box: 56, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 56, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Migration of Farm People, Publication (Box 56, Folder 51)
- Box: 57, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Migration and Development in the West Indies, Publication (Box 57, Folder 1)
    Author: Edwin P. Reubens
- Box: 57, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Guide to Seasonal Farm Work Areas in the Eastern Seaboard States, 1951; Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Author: U.S. Employment Service
  - Item 2: Wheat and Small-Grain Harvest Map of the Great Plains States, Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: A Guide to Seasonal Farm Work Areas in the Far Western States, Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Your Guide to Farm Jobs in the Intermountain States, 1950; Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Your Guide to Farm Jobs from the Gulf to Great Lakes, 1949; Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Notes: April 1949
  - Item 6: Progress Report on Migratory Labor Legislation, 1963; Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Use of Domestic and Foreign Migratory Agricultural Workers, 1952; Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Author: U.S. Office of Defense Mobilization
    Notes: November 29, 1952
  - Item 8: The Education of Migrant Children, Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: No Harvest for the Reaper, Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Author: Herbert Hill
  - Item 10: Atlantic Coast Migratory Movement of Agricultural Workers, Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Author: C.W.E. Pittman
  - Item 11: The Starve that We May Eat, Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Author: Edith E. Lowry
  - Item 12: Migrant Labor, a Human Problem, 1947; Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Notes: March 1947
  - Item 13: The Wetback Invasion - Illegal Alien Labor in American Agriculture, 1951; Publication (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Author: Frank L. Auerbach
    Notes: May 3, 1951
- Box: 57, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Journal of Modern African Studies, Publication (Box 57, Folder 3)
    Author: David & Helen Kimble
- Box: 57, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Migratory Labour in South Africa, 1967; Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    Author: Peter Randall
  - Item 2: The Gold of Migrant Labour, 1961; Publication (Box 57, Folder 4)
    Author: Ruth First
- Box: 57, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Transients and Migrants, 1939; Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    Author: Victor Jones
    Notes: February 27, 1939
  - Item 2: The Effect of Misreported Social Security Account Numbers on Agricultural Worker Mobility Statistics, 1965; Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    Notes: October 5, 1965
  - Item 3: Narrative & Minutes of the Conference on Fresno's Migrant Labor Center, 1963; Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
    Author: Donald L. Pollard
    Notes: June 7, 1963
  - Item 4: The California Migrant Farm Worker, His Family, and the Rural Community, Publication (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Box: 57, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Migratory Labor in Colorado, 1960; Publication (Box 57, Folder 6)
    Author: Colorado Legislative Council
- Box: 57, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The EEC and the Migration of Workers, Publication (Box 57, Folder 7)
    Author: W.R. Bohning & David Stephen
- Box: 57, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Housing for Florida's Migrants, 1958; Publication (Box 57, Folder 8)
    Author: U.S. Deparment of Labor
    Notes: August 1958
  - Item 2: Migrant Project, 1959; Publication (Box 57, Folder 8)
    Author: Florida State Board of Health
    Notes: July 1959
- Box: 57, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Ten Years of Progress in Idaho for Migrant Workers, 1966; Publication (Box 57, Folder 9)
    Author: The Governor's Migratory Labor Committee
- Box: 57, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: County Profile of Agricultural Migrant Workers in Illinois, Publication (Box 57, Folder 10)
    Author: Illinois Commission on Children
- Box: 57, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Report on The Louisiana Migrant Labor Problem, 1960; Publication (Box 57, Folder 11)
    Author: The Louisiana Interdepartmental Committee
- Box: 57, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Health Services for Migratory and Seasonal Agricultural Workers, 1969; Publication (Box 57, Folder 12)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce
    Notes: September 29, 1969
  - Item 2: Health Clinics for Migratory Farm Workers, 1962; Publication (Box 57, Folder 12)
    Notes: February 15, 1962
- Box: 57, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Seasonal Farm Workers in New Jersey, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
    Author: New Jersey Office of Economic Opportunity
  - Item 2: Digest Migrant Labor Code, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
    Author: New Jersey Department of Labor and Industry
  - Item 3: Migrant Labor Act, 1945; Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: If You Plan to Work on New Jersey Farms Read This and Save It, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
    Author: New Jersey State Employment Service
  - Item 5: New Jersey Farmers and Migrant Housing Rules, Publication (Box 57, Folder 13)
    Author: Richard A. Hogarty
- Box: 57, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Domestic Migratory Farm Labor, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Author: U.S. President's Committee on Migratory Labor
  - Item 2: Next Move for the Migrants, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Author: William E. Scholes
  - Item 3: Domestic Migratory Farmworkers, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Impact of Federal Programs to Improve the Living Conditions of Migrant and Other Seasonal Farmworkers, 1973; Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Notes: February 6, 1973
  - Item 5: Migratory Labor, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Author: Michael J. Calvin
  - Item 6: Migratory Labor and Low Income Farmers, 1957; Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Author: National Sharecroppers Fund
    Notes: November 13, 1957
  - Item 7: Migratory Agricultural Labor in the U.S., 1953; Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Author: Josiah C. Folsom
  - Item 8: This is the Migrant, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Author: Louisa Rossiter Shotwell
  - Item 9: Toward a National Policy for Migrant Labor, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Author: Catholic Council on Working Life
  - Item 10: No Work Today!, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Author: Varden Fuller
  - Item 11: They Follow the Sun, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Author: E.L. Koos
  - Item 12: Domestic Migratory Farm Labor, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Author: President's Committee on Migratory Labor
  - Item 13: This is How 12 Camps for Migratory Workers in Agriculture are Operated, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: Entry of Mexican Agricultural Workers into the United States, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 15: Proceedings: Western Interstate Conference on Migratory Labor, 1960; Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Author: Western Interstate Conference on Migratory Labor
    Notes: April 10-13, 1960
  - Item 16: Down on the Farm, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 17: Migratory Farmworkers in the Midcontinent Streams, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 18: Children in Migrant Families, 1960; Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Appropriations
  - Item 19: Program Activities Under the Migrant Health Act, 1964; Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Notes: June 30, 1964
  - Item 20: The Farm Workers, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 21: Selected State Programs in Migrant Education, Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Item 22: Federal Government Viewpoint Concerning Mexican Migratory Labor, 1957; Publication (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Author: E.L. Keenan
    Notes: February 3, 1957
- Box: 57, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Rules, Regulations and Laws that Affect Seasonal Farm and Food Processing Workers and Their Employers, 1963; Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
    Author: New York State Interdepartmental Committee on Farm and Food Processing Labor
  - Item 2: Migratory Labor in New York State, Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
    Author: Anne M. Montero
  - Item 3: Child Labor on Truck Farms in New York State, 1939; Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
    Author: New York Child Labor Committee
  - Item 4: A Helping Hand, 1963; Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
    Author: State of New York
  - Item 5: Sweatshops in the Sun, 1952; Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
    Author: Alexander L. Crosby
  - Item 6: Migrant Farm Labor in New York State, 1961; Publication (Box 57, Folder 15)
    Author: New York State Interdepartmental Committee
- Box: 57, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Migrant Workers in Ohio, 1961; Publication (Box 57, Folder 16)
    Author: Ohio Legislative Service Commission
  - Item 2: Migratory Labor in Ohio, Publication (Box 57, Folder 16)
    Author: The Governor's Committee on Migrant Labor
  - Item 3: Migratory Labor in Ohio, Publication (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Box: 57, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Labour Migration in a Rural Economy, Publication (Box 57, Folder 17)
    Author: P.H. Gulliver
- Box: 57, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Migratory Labor Movement and Licensed Texas Labor Statistics, Publication (Box 57, Folder 18)
    Author: Texas Bureau of Labor Statistics
  - Item 2: Report on Migratory Labor Movement and Licensed Texas Labor Agents, Publication (Box 57, Folder 18)
- Box: 57, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Migratory Agricultural Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Migratory Workers and Their Families, 1956; Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
    Notes: April 1956
  - Item 3: Migratory Workers and Their Families, 1955; Publication (Box 57, Folder 19)
- Box: 57, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: How the Migrant Agricultural Worker and His Family Have Fared Under the Economic Opportunity Act, Publication (Box 57, Folder 20)
- Box: 57, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Migratory Workers in Cucumber Harvesting, 1964; Publication (Box 57, Folder 21)
    Author: University of Wisconsin
- Box: 57, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: How Two Companies Handle Military Leave, Publication (Box 57, Folder 22)
- Box: 57, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Manpower Need of the Armed Services, 1943; Publication (Box 57, Folder 23)
    Author: Harry S. Truman
    Notes: September 21, 1943
- Box: 57, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Mill and His Early Critics, Publication (Box 57, Folder 24)
    Author: J.C. Rees
- Box: 57, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Growth and Concentration in the Flour Milling Industry, 1947; Publication (Box 57, Folder 25)
    Author: U.S. Federal Trade Commission
- Box: 57, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Explosion at Hapton Valley Colliery, Lancashire, 1962; Publication (Box 57, Folder 26)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Power
    Notes: November 1962
- Box: 57, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Employment and Injuries in the Metal and Nonmetal Industries, Publication (Box 57, Folder 27)
    Author: Forrest T. Moyer
  - Item 2: Injury Experience in the Metallic Mineral Industries, 1969; Publication (Box 57, Folder 27)
    Author: U.S. Department of the Interior
- Box: 57, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Mineral Industry Map of Ohio, Publication (Box 57, Folder 28)
- Box: 57, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Dealing with Health and Safety in the Mineral and Allied Industries, 1946; Publication (Box 57, Folder 29)
- Box: 57, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Federal Metal and Nonmetallic Mine Safety Act, 1965; Publication (Box 57, Folder 30)
    Notes: July 8, 1965
- Box: 57, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: State Employees Handbook, Publication (Box 57, Folder 31)
    Author: Minnesota Department of Civil Service
  - Item 2: Protection of Minorities, 1967; Publication (Box 57, Folder 31)
- Box: 57, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Overseas Chinese Education in Indonesia, Publication (Box 57, Folder 32)
- Box: 57, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Negroes and Mexican Americans in South and East Los Angeles, 1966; Publication (Box 57, Folder 33)
- Box: 57, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Selected Statistics for Counties of New York State, Publication (Box 57, Folder 34)
    Author: New York Division of Human Rights
  - Item 2: Racial and Ethnic Composition of Work Force or Union Membership, Publication (Box 57, Folder 34)
    Author: California Fair Employment Practice Commission
  - Item 3: Nonwhites and the "Population Explosion" in New York State, Publication (Box 57, Folder 34)
- Box: 57, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Research Data on Minority Groups, Publication (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: Not Just Some of Us, Publication (Box 57, Folder 35)
- Box: 57, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Pyramiding of Profits and Costs in the Missile Procurement Program, 1964; Publication (Box 57, Folder 36)
    Notes: March 31, 1964
  - Item 2: Missiles, Spacecraft, and Aircraft, 1963; Publication (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: Aerospace Employment, 1965; Publication (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Item 4: Missiles and Aircraft, 1962; Publication (Box 57, Folder 36)
- Box: 57, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Salaries of State Employees: Missouri and Selected States, 1950; Publication (Box 57, Folder 37)
    Author: Missouri Committee on Legislative Research
- Box: 57, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Money and Credit, Publication (Box 57, Folder 38)
    Author: Commission on Money and Credit
- Box: 57, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Stochastic Optimization and Microeconomic Theory, Publication (Box 57, Folder 39)
    Author: V. Mukerji
- Box: 57, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 57, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Apologists for Monopoly, Publication (Box 57, Folder 40)
    Author: International Publishers
  - Item 2: Legality of Service Associations, Publication (Box 57, Folder 40)
    Author: Textile Finishers Association
  - Item 3: What's the Use of Working?, 1931; Publication (Box 57, Folder 40)
    Author: Robert Bruce Brinsmade
    Notes: January 1931
  - Item 4: Billionaire Corporations, Publication (Box 57, Folder 40)
- Box: 57, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 57, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Montana Retirement Laws, 1967; Publication (Box 57, Folder 41)
    Author: Montana Board of Administration
- Box: 57, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 57, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Who are the Working Mothers?, Publication (Box 57, Folder 42)
- Box: 58, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Beroepsarbeid Buitenshuis Door Vrouwen Met Gevinsverantwoordelijkheid, 1966; Publication (Box 58, Folder 1)
    Author: Minister van Cultuur Recreatie en Maatschappelijk Werk
- Box: 58, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Working Mothers, Publication (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Author: Business and Professional Women's Foundation
- Box: 58, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Mt. ISA, 1966; Publication (Box 58, Folder 3)
    Author: Bretta Carthey & Bob Potter
- Box: 58, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: How Do You Transfer the Homeowner?, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    Author: John W. Angle
- Box: 58, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Executive Behavior, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Competitive Factor in Employee Performance, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Author: R.P. Calhoon
  - Item 3: Action Guide to Motivating People, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Author: Bureau of Business Practice
  - Item 4: Motivation, 1964; Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Author: Michigan Civil Service Commission
  - Item 5: Motivation and the Automation of Training, 1962; Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Author: Alvin Ugelow
  - Item 6: Motivations, 1954; Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Author: Business Week
    Notes: August 14, 1954
  - Item 7: Staff Motivation, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Author: Stanley L. Bozdech, Lawrence C. Hackamack
  - Item 8: Motivation: Maslow vs. Herzberg, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Author: James L. Dougherty
  - Item 9: The Role of Motivation in Communication, 1963; Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: How to Motivate People, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Author: Richard M. Miller
- Box: 58, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Films for Employee Training and Customer Showings, Publication (Box 58, Folder 6)
    Author: National Association of Food Chains
  - Item 2: Visual Communication Ideas for Management, 1966; Publication (Box 58, Folder 6)
    Author: Film and Audio-Visual Annual
- Box: 58, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Film Production and Management, Publication (Box 58, Folder 7)
    Author: Michael Balcon
- Box: 58, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Difference Between the Film Artistes' Association and the Film Production Association, Publication (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Box: 58, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: City Government Finances in 1963, Publication (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Box: 58, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Personnel Practices, Wages and Salaries: Municipal Public Works Departments, 1950; Publication (Box 58, Folder 10)
    Author: American Public Works Association
- Box: 58, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Problems Arising from the Cyclical Pattern of Machine Tool Orders, Publication (Box 58, Folder 11)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Technology
- Box: 58, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Remunertaion and Expense Allowance Paid to Mayors and Members of Council, 1968; Publication (Box 58, Folder 12)
    Author: Canadian Federation of Mayors and Municipalities
    Language: English; French.
- Box: 58, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Wages, Salaries and Fringe Benefits in Colorado Cities and Towns, Publication (Box 58, Folder 13)
    Author: Colorado Municipal League
- Box: 58, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Full-Time Police & Fire Personnel in Connecticut, 1965; Publication (Box 58, Folder 14)
    Author: Connecticut Public Expenditure Council
- Box: 58, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Town and County Hall, Publication (Box 58, Folder 15)
    Author: The Acton Society Trust
- Box: 58, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Salaries and Fringe Benefits in Idaho Municipalities, Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
    Author: William O. Lewis & Katherine D. Pell
  - Item 2: Idaho Municipal Salaries, 1966; Publication (Box 58, Folder 16)
    Author: Herbert Sidney Duncombe & Katherine D. Pell
- Box: 58, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Directory of Municipal Personnel Agencies, 1968; Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
    Author: Massachusetts Municipal Personnel Association
    Notes: July 15, 1968
  - Item 2: Central New York Profile, 1968; Publication (Box 58, Folder 17)
    Author: Metropolitan Development Association
- Box: 58, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Forty-First Annual Directory of Michigan Municipal Officials, 1968; Publication (Box 58, Folder 18)
    Author: Michigan Municipal League
- Box: 58, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Municipal Salaries, Wages and Fringe Benefits of Officials and Employees in North Carolina Towns, 1967; Publication (Box 58, Folder 19)
    Author: North Carolina League of Municipalities
- Box: 58, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Police and Firemen's Pension Funds, Publication (Box 58, Folder 20)
- Box: 58, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Salary Rates and Fringe Benefits in Municipal Employment, 1966; Publication (Box 58, Folder 21)
- Box: 58, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Personnel Administration in Virginia Municipalities, 1962; Publication (Box 58, Folder 22)
    Author: Virginia Municipal League
  - Item 2: A Merit System for Municipal Personnel, 1962; Publication (Box 58, Folder 22)
    Notes: April 1962
  - Item 3: The Berkeley Project: Race and Socio-Economic Status in the Selection Testing of Municipal Personnel, 1966; Publication (Box 58, Folder 22)
    Author: John C. Bianchini
  - Item 4: Personnel Manual for Municipalities, 1960; Publication (Box 58, Folder 22)
    Author: John C. Buechner
- Box: 58, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Fringe Benefits in Rhode Island Cities & Towns, Publication (Box 58, Folder 23)